360.io 2018-11-26

# Occipital - Privacy

## Information we collect

_Account Information_. When you download or install Software, create an account, or purchase something from us, we collect and store your name, address, email and any other information you provide to us in connection with your registration and/or purchase.

_Communications_. We retain records of your communications with us, such as emails, forum posts and Twitter tags.

_Content_. If you upload Content from the Software or for purposes of using the Services, we retain and store the Content and we collect data and information regarding the nature or composition of that Content (e.g., the elements in a room converted uploaded to Canvas).

_Hardware Information_. Every time you connect Hardware to the Internet, we collect information about that hardware such as device identifier, device type, language and region settings, timestamp, and calendar type.

_Software Information_. Some Software is location-enabled. If you allow your device to transmit location data (such as GPS-signal), we collect this information and associate it with your Content.

_Third-Party Sites_. We collect and store information that allows you to link or share your Content to other sites such as Twitter and Facebook. We collect and store information about you from those third-party sites, such as your full name. Any Content that you share to those third-party sites is governed by the privacy policies of those sites.

_Website Information_. We collect data, including IP address, and analytics about the scope and duration of your visits to our websites and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. This information includes, characters you type, your search and browsing history, services and links you click, and pages and content you view. We may keep a record of your various actions during your visits to our websites including using such methods as cookies and single pixel images. We do not respond to browser-based "do not track" signals.

## How we use your information

_General Uses_. We use your Content and other information to:

  * Provide you with the products and services that we offer, communicate with you, respond to your inquiries, provide troubleshooting, and for other customer service purposes.
  * Send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you, including information about third party products and services.
  * Conduct analysis and gather metrics to better understand how users access and use the products and services, to evaluate and improve the Occipital products and services, and to develop new products and services.
  * Advertise Occipital products and services to you on non-Occipital websites and measure the effectiveness of that advertising.
  * Comply with legal obligations, as part of our general business operations, and for other business administration purposes.
  * Market our products and services, by re-displaying or re-transmitting Content that you have already displayed in public areas of our Services or website.

_Research_. If you provide a Research Consent for a piece of Content (which is in addition to the consent in which you accept our Terms), we may use that particular piece of Content in data sets we use for for commercial or non-commercial research and development (the “Research Data”). We will not include any personally identifiable metadata such as IP address, precise location, email addresses, or names in Research Data. However, we may not remove imagery contained within your Content that can identify you or others (e.g., pictures of faces, street views, facades, etc.). You are responsible for removing or avoiding capture of any identifying data in your Content, and we are not responsible for any failure on your part to do so. Once your Content has been included in Research Data it cannot be removed.

## Sharing your Content and information

_Service providers_. We share information with service providers who help us provide products and services. These include website analytics tools, payment service providers, information technology providers, and companies to whom we outsource elements of our services such as customer support. These service providers all adhere by this Privacy Policy as if they are Occipital.

_Sale of Occipital_. We may disclose or transfer your Content or information, including personal information, as part of any merger, sale, and transfer of our assets, acquisition or restructuring of all or part of our business, bankruptcy, or similar event.

_Advertising Partners_. We share anonymized information about your use of the Occipital websites (including IP address) with Google, Facebook and other third parties so that we can present you with advertising on non-Occipital websites and measure the effectiveness of that advertising.

_Legally required disclosure_. We reserve the right to disclose information if we believe that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) protect or defend the rights or property of us or users of the services.

_Research_. If you consent to include your Content in our Research Data, we may share the Research Data with with entities outside of Occipital for purposes of research and development . These entities may include academic or industry researchers, teams within other companies, or individuals. We may share the Research Data with a usage license, or with no restrictions at all and the Content may be included in published research or in publicly available downloadable datasets You cannot revoke this consent.

_Third parties with whom you share Content_. Any Content that you share with other parties, including through third-party sites such as Twitter or Facebook, is governed by the privacy policies of those sites. We are not responsibility for the protection or use of your data that you share with others.

_Notice to California Residents_. A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (a "California Customer") may request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal data was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal data that were disclosed. California Customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing privacy@occipital.com. Please note that we are required to respond to one request per California Customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

## Managing your Content and information

You may opt-out of any promotional emails we send by following the instructions in the email you receive. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you emails related to your account or transactions thereunder, or notices of any updates to our Terms or this Policy.

You may opt-out of sharing location from your device by disabling location features entirely for the Software from your device settings (the exact steps to do so will vary based on your device).

You may choose not to create an account thus avoid giving us your name and email address, although many features may require the creation of an account. If you do create an account, you can access and either edit or delete personally identifiable information such as name and email address through your account.

You can elect not to use cookies by disabling them in your browser settings or electing to not accept cookies the first time you visit one of our sites. If you want to disable cookies after having accepted them you can follow [this link](https://www.lifewire.com/how-to-delete-cookies-2617981) for instructions to remove cookies from your machine.

You may ask us to delete your account or any Content or other information about you that we hold by contacting us at privacy@occipital.com. We may retain copies of some portions of your personal information for up to 180 days after your request as a part of our system backups and to ensure we have the information required for purchase related disputes.

## How we protect your information

We use industry standard methods designed to protect the transmission of sensitive information such as your password during transmission such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If you create an account with Occipital, your personal private information is protected by a password or other authentication mechanism for security. We do not store any payment card or bank account information. You are responsible for taking appropriate actions to protect your account such as using secure passwords and making sure to log out when finished using a shared device or computer.

## Additional Notes

_United States Processing_. Your information will be processed in the United States, where laws regarding processing of information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

_13 and Older_. You may only upload Content to our Services if you are at least 13 years old or older. You should not upload any Content to your Services if you are not at least 13 years old.
